- What happened to your group?
- Dumped them. They're a bunch of wussies.
(Penny:)Frenzy stance.
(Penny:)Frenzy, frenzy, frenzy.
(Sheldon:)So listen,
would you describe your ideal vacation...
(Sheldon:)...as a wild adventure to unknown lands
or staying at home with a good book?
- Wait, what?
- These are market-research questions.
(Sheldon:)I'm filling out the online registration
for your game.
(Penny:)Oh, okay, wild adventure.
(Penny:)Oh, frenzy stance isn't working.
(Penny:)- Die, you undead mummy, die!
- Drink a healing potion.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Anyhow, on a scale of one to five...
...with one being, "always initiated by him"
and five being, "always initiated by you"...
(Sheldon:)...how do you prefer
your sexual encounters to begin?
(Penny:)That's on the registration?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes, it's quite extensive.
(Sheldon:)If we complete it,
you get a free expansion pack.
Seventy-five additional quests.
(Penny:)Oh, awesome. Okay, I totally like to initiate.
I'm a big old five.